http://www.millernurseries.com/about/privacy-policy

Fruit Trees
Shop All Fruit Trees »
Apple TreesApricot TreesBanana PlantsCherry TreesCitrus TreesDogwood TreesFig TreesMulberry Trees
Nectarine TreesOlive TreesPawpaw TreesPeach TreesPear TreesPersimmon TreesPlum TreesPomegranate Trees
Popular Searches
Disease-Resistant Fruit TreesDwarf Fruit TreesFruit Tree CollectionsHeirloom Fruit TreesIndoor Fruit TreesMulti-Grafted Fruit TreesSemi-Dwarf Fruit TreesStandard Fruit TreesStark Picks
Featured Item
Pennsylvania Golden Pawpaw
$61.99
(23)
Nut Trees
Shop All Nut Trees »
Almond TreesChestnut TreesFilbert Hazelnut TreesPecan TreesWalnut Trees
Popular Searches
Black Walnut TreesSelf-Pollinating Pecan Trees
Featured Item
Pawnee Pecan
Starting at $48.99
(20)
Landscape Trees
Shop All Landscape Trees »
Flowering TreesShade Trees
Popular Searches
Maple TreesRedbud Trees
Featured Item
Red Sunset® Maple
$49.99
(10)
Berry Plants
Shop All Berry Plants »
Berry Plant AssortmentsAronia Berry PlantsBlackberry PlantsBlueberry PlantsCranberry PlantsCurrant PlantsElderberry PlantsGoji Berry Plants
Gooseberry PlantsGrape VinesHoneyberry PlantsHybrid Berry PlantsKiwi Berry VinesLingonberry PlantsRaspberry PlantsStrawberry Plants
Popular Searches
Berry Plant CollectionsBushel and Berry®Everbearing StrawberriesJune Bearing StrawberriesPrimocane BerriesSeedless GrapesThornless BlackberriesThornless Raspberries
Featured Item
Anna Hardy Kiwi
Starting at $26.99
(7)
Garden Plants
Shop All Garden Plants »
Asparagus PlantsHerbsHop BinesHorseradish PlantsHydrangeasLilacsOnion PlantsOrganic Seed Potatoes
Rhubarb PlantsRosesSweet Potato PlantsWeigelaWisteriaAdditional Garden PlantsGarden Plant Assortments
Popular Searches
Garden Plant CollectionsGarlic PlantsKnock Out® Roses
Featured Item
Pink Double Knock Out® Rose
$19.99
(28)
Tools & Supplies
Shop All Tools & Supplies »
BooksGift Certificates & Seasonal ItemsKitchen & Canning SuppliesPest & Disease ControlsSoil AdditivesSuccess KitsTools & EquipmentTree AccessoriesWildlife Feeders & Houses
Popular Searches
Digital Soil MetersGarden NettingGift IdeasHarvesting SuppliesIrrigation SolutionsNatural Pest & Disease ControlOrganic-Growing SuppliesPruning ToolsStark® Fertilizers
Featured Item
Stark® Tree Guards
Starting at $8.99 / 3 Pack
(243)
Organic
Organic Products
Organic Apple Trees
Organic Seed Potatoes
Organic-Growing Supplies
Organic Resources
Lasagna GardeningOrganic Growing Myths & MistakesPreventing Problems Before They BeginThe Best Fruit-Tree Varieties for Organic GrowingGrowing More “Perfect” Organic FruitWatering & Conservation
All Organic Products & Resources »
The Stark Organic Story »
Growing Guide
How-To Guides »
How to Grow Apple TreesHow to Grow Peach TreesHow to Grow Grape VinesHow to Grow Pear TreesHow to Grow RosesHow to Grow Cherry TreesHow to Grow Blueberry PlantsHow to Grow Plum TreesHow to Grow Flowering Trees
See All the How-To Guides »
Article Categories
Frequently Asked QuestionsFruit Tree CareHow To GrowIdeas & InspirationOrganicProduct FeaturesProjects & IdeasProjects & PlanningRecipesRetail LocationStoriesVideoWholesale
See the Latest Articles »
Featured Article
Adding Fruit to Your Homestead
For over 200 years, Stark Bro's Nursery has been helping homesteaders across America live more self-sufficient lifestyles.
As the oldest continually operating nursery in the country, we've curated a time-tested collection of over 300 unique varieties of fruit trees, nut trees and berry plants.
Read more »
Free shipping on orders over $125!
A Note from Stark Bro's on Coronavirus (COVID-19) »
Stark Bro's
About Stark Bro'sPrivacy Policy & Terms of Use
Terms of Use & Privacy Policy
Protecting your privacy is very important to us. This page describes our policies and procedures regarding the way we use, disclose, share and protect your personal information and/or data in your Stark Bro's website account. This Privacy Policy applies to activities by Stark Bro's Nurseries & Orchards Co. and its affiliates and subsidiaries (collectively "Stark Bro's", "we" or "us").
What kind of information does Stark Bro's collect online?
We collect information directly from individuals, from third parties, and automatically through the Stark Bro's website.This includes the use of a third-party rating and review tool. Users of the rating and review service give consent to have their reviews and comments collected and potentially published on our website, or elsewhere. These reviews and comments can include certain biographical information such as name, alias, or location.
We use cookies, pixel tags, and other tracking technologies to automatically collect information about your activities, such as your searches, page views, date and time of your visit, and other information about your use of the Stark Bro's website. We also collect information that your computer or mobile device provides to us in connection with your use of the Stark Bro's website such as your browser type, type of computer or mobile device, IP address, mobile carrier, unique device identifier, location, and requested and referring URLs.
In addition, when you visit our website, we make use of remarketing and similar audience systems from third-party vendors, including Google and other services for Display Advertisers features, to show ads on sites across the Internet. These third-party vendors use cookies to serve ads based on past visits to our website.
How does Stark Bro's protect my information online?
We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology with verified information though DigiCert to protect your online order information as it is transmitted over the Internet. We also utilize advanced firewall technology to protect our equipment from online attacks.
Some versions of browsers and firewalls do not permit communication through secure servers like the ones we use at starkbros.com. To check the security of your Internet connection, look at your browser window after accessing our website, prior to entering your credit card information. An unbroken key icon or a closed lock icon will indicate that SSL is active. You can also double-check the security by looking at the URL line of your browser. When accessing a secure server, the first characters of the site address will change from "http:" to "https:".
If your browser or firewall does not support SSL, you will not be able to connect to the server. This also means you will not be able to mistakenly place an order through an unsecured connection. If for any reason you cannot access our secure server, you can place your order by phone at 800.325.4180.
Do I have a choice with the use of my information?
You have the options to review, change or modify the use of your personal information in regards to promotional emails, catalog mailings, third-party sharing, and promotional telephone contact. If you have a starkbros.com, all of these options can be found on the Promotion Options page of your account. If your account is not yet set up online, you can simply call us at 800.325.4180 to make any of these inquiries or changes. We respect your wishes concerning the use of your personal information.
You can also opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the Ads Preference Manager. You can opt out of third-party vendors use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page. And you can install a browser add-on to opt out of Google Analytics data collection.
Can I resell the products I ordered?
Stark Bro's represents and warrants that our products are not eligible for resale under any circumstance. Additionally, third-party sellers are prohibited by law from any unauthorized first-sale of Stark Bro's products or misrepresentations/unauthorized use of Stark Bro's intellectual property. Violators will be held responsible.
Have additional questions or concerns?
Should you have any additional questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy, or if you need to correct or change any account information, please contact us.
Our Company
About Stark Bro's
Contact Information
E-Newsletter
Frequently Asked Questions
Glossary of Terms
Hardiness Zone Finder
Hours of Operation
Terms of Use & Privacy Policy
Share:
Subscribe to e-newslettersfor timely offers & advice
OK
About Stark Bro's
A growing legacy since 1816. For over 200 years, Stark Bro's has helped people around America provide delicious home-grown food for their families.
Read about the Stark Bro's history that spans over 200 years »
Stay Connected
We love to keep in touch with our customers and talk about what's happening each season at Stark Bro's. Follow us on your favorite social networks and share what you grow!
Facebook
Pinterest
Twitter
Instagram
YouTube
Questions or Comments?
You'll find answers to many questions on our FAQ page. If you need further assistance, we're always eager to help.
Chat:
Start Live Chat
Email:
info@starkbros.com
Phone:
800.325.4180
Fax:
573.754.3701
Mail:
PO BOX 1800Louisiana, MO 63353
Our Company
About Stark Bro's
Contact Information
E-Newsletters
Frequently Asked Questions
Gift Certificates
Glossary of Terms
Terms of Use & Privacy Policy
* Free Shipping does not apply to orders shipping to Alaska. (A $50 surcharge will be added for shipments to Alaska.) © 2020 Stark Bro's Nurseries & Orchards Co.
AnnouncementLoading, please waitClose
We have some big news...We're joining with Stark Bro's!
Dear Friends,
I'm very excited to announce that after 75 years, Miller Nurseries will now become part of Stark Bro's, a highly respected nursery company that's been "growing" their famous legacy since 1816.
Who is Stark Bro's?
Hear the president of Stark Bro's, Cameron Brown, and others tell the Stark Bro's story.
For over 200 years, Stark Bro's has been producing high-quality fruit trees, berries and garden plants for gardeners like you. With their great nursery stock and expert advice, they've been helping generations of families reap not only the rewards of growing their own fruits and nuts, but to enjoy huge savings in the process. Stark Bro's has a long-standing reputation for quality, honesty and really taking care of their customers.
When my brother David passed away suddenly last spring, I knew it was time to retire. One of the first things I did was to call Cameron Brown, the president of Stark Bro's. He is a long-time friend and a very trustworthy fellow, and treats his customers like gold. I knew he would take care of you in exactly the same way. David would have liked this arrangement, and I take comfort in that.
What's going to happen to Miller Nurseries and my customer account?
It's only going to get better as part of the Stark Bro's family. You'll now be able to come here to StarkBros.com and sign in with your existing username and password, and purchase products just like you did on the Miller Nurseries website... only the selection will be much larger! You'll still be able to buy Miller's familiar "Canandaigua Quality" hardy plants as well as the enormous assortment of trees and plants Stark Bro's offers.
We want to take this opportunity to acknowledge our family, our wonderful employees, and especially you - our loyal customers - for your support and patronage over these last 75 years. Thank you for being such an important part of our heritage.
Warm regards,
John Miller, CEO
Miller Nurseries
Questions or concerns about the change?
Contact Us »
We're happy to answer all your questions.
